http://www.dart.biz/privacy-policy/

×
Our Response to Coronavirus (COVID-19): We’re supporting our employees, customers and frontline healthcare workers. Learn More
Region Select
United States
Canada (English)
Canada (français)
Cups
Diverse cup options for your hot and cold beverage needs.
Dinnerware
Plates and bowls made from plastic, paper, foam or sugarcane.
Lids
Durable, tight-fitting lids for hot and cold cups.
Product Literature
Download product specs, industry facts and more
Containers
A wide range of to-go containers for all business types.
Accessories
Cutlery and other accessories to enjoy food on the go.
Consumer
Cups and plates packaged for resale.
Literature en Español
Descargue especificaciones de productos, datos de la industria y más en español
Patent Search
Let us help you search Dart patent information by product stock code.
Privacy Policy for Dart Container Corporation
Effective Date: February 2017; Last Updated: December 31, 2019
This Privacy Policy Applies to the Sites Where It Appears.
This policy describes Dart Container Corporation’s information collection and use practices. It applies to information we collect from you when you interact with us.
We Collect Categories of Information From and About You.
Dart collects the below categories of information. An explanation of each of these categories is described here.
Contact information. We collect your name and email address. We also collect your physical address and phone number. We may also collect your company name.
Payment information. If you make purchases with us we collect your customer number and billing address.
Employment information. We collect resume, education, and employment history from applicants and employees. We also collect certification credentials and driver’s license information. We collect bank account information from employees.
Site usage information. We collect information about the browser you are using. We also collect information about the sites you came from and where you visit when you leave us. We may also collect your operating system and IP address.
We Use Your Information As Described.
We use the categories of information for the business and commercial purposes outlined here:
We use information to respond to your requests or questions. We use your contact information to respond to your questions, including customer service requests. This includes questions about our products or your relationship with us. We use employment information to process your application.
We use information to improve products and services. We use your site usage information to improve our sites and services. We use your contact and site usage information to customize your experience with us.
We use information for employment purposes. We use employment information to provide payroll and benefits. We also use it for performance management.
We use information for security purposes. We may use all categories of information to protect our company and our customers. We may also use your site information to protect our sites.
We use information for marketing purposes. We use your contact information to provide you with information about products and special promotions. We may also use your contact and site usage information to serve you with ads and offers. We do this when legally permitted.
We use information to communicate about our relationship. We will use your contact information to contact you about this Privacy Policy or other terms. We will also use your contact information to correspond with you about your account.
We use information to process orders. We may use contact and payment information to provide service to that order.
We use information as otherwise described and permitted by law.
If you are in Europe: Our basis for processing your information is typically to perform a contract. Performance of a contract includes responding to your request. We also process information based on consent or for our legitimate interest.
We Collect Information In a Variety of Ways.
We collect information directly from you. We collect contact and payment information when you place an order. It could also be on our sites. We collect employment information when you apply for a job with us.
We collect information about you passively. We use tracking tools to collect site usage information from you passively. Tracking tools include browser cookies and web beacons. This includes usage and browser information. We do this on our websites and in emails that we send to you. We collect information about users over time when you use our websites.
We get information about you from third parties. We collect contact and site usage information from our business partners. This includes social media sites.
We Combine Information We Get About You.
We combine information that we have collected offline with information that we collect online as permitted by law. We combine information we have collected across other third-party sites. We combine information collected across devices, such as computers and mobile devices. We also combine information that we get from a third party with information we already have.
We Share Information With Others.
We share your information with vendors who perform services on our behalf. We may share your contact information with trusted service providers.  These include companies who help us deliver products or services to you. We share employment information with vendors who help administer benefit services or other human resource administration.
We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We will also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. This includes U.S. and non-U.S. law enforcement or regulatory authorities.
We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business. If all or part of our business was sold, we may share contact information and payment as part of that transaction. If there is a merger or acquisition, we may also share your contact and payment information. Where legally required, we will give you prior notice and if you have the legal right to do so, allow you to object.
We may share information with our business partners. We may also jointly collect contact information with third parties. This might include promotion partners.
We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you or as permitted by law.
You Have Certain Choices About How We Use Your Information.
We provide you with options on how we use your information, as described here:
You can opt out of certain marketing. To stop receiving our marketing communications please email us at wmc@dart.biz or follow the instructions in any message you get from us.  If you opt out of marketing emails you will continue to receive messages from us about your relationship with us where permitted by law.
You can control cookies and tracking tools. To learn how to manage how we and our vendors use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our Do Not Track policy, please click here.
California residents’ rights. If you reside in California and are not a job applicant, contractor, employee, or employee of another company interacting with us in your job role, you have the right to request what information we collect, use, and disclose. You also have the right to request that we delete your information. To make a request, you can contact us by clicking here if you are a consumer and here if you are an employee or job applicant. In the alternative you can call us at 833-472-3278. We will use information you provide to us to verify your request by matching information you provide with information we have about you. We will not discriminate against you because you have exercised any of your privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act. You can designate an agent to make a request by having them execute a notarized power of attorney to act on your behalf.
Sales of personal information. Under California law, we are required to tell you if we “sell” information as that term is defined by applicable law. “Sell” means to share personal information with a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration. We do not sell your personal information based on our understanding of that term. We also have disclosure obligations in Nevada. We do not exchange Nevada residents’ personal information for money with anyone so they may license or sell the personal information to additional parties. We do not sell personal information of minors under the age of 16. Nevada residents may opt out of the future sale of their information to a third party so that they may license or sell information by emailing us at: hrconnect@dart.biz. You may contact us with questions or requests regarding the sale of your information at 833-472-3278wmc@dart.biz.
EU Residents. As required by law, you have certain rights. This includes a right to access, correct, and erase your information. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority. Please contact us at hrconnect@dart.biz to exercise your rights.
Our Sites Are Not Intended for Children.
Our sites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can contact us at the email or address above. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.”
Parents can learn more about how to protect children's privacy online here.
We Use Standard Security Measures.
We use appropriate and reasonable security measures as required by relevant law. The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet.
We May Store and Use Information Both Inside and Outside of the United States
Information we collect may be stored and processed in the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. The United States may not afford the same level of protection as the laws in your country. By submitting your information you agree to the processing of it in the US as permitted by law. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.
We May Link to Other Sites Or Have Third Party Services On Our Site We Don’t Control.
We may link to third-party sites. Our sites may also include third party content that collects information. We do not control these third parties. This Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Please read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for the practices of these third-party sites.
You Can Contact Us About This Policy and Your Information.
If you have other questions about this Policy or our privacy practices please email us at hrconnect@dart.biz.  You can also call us at 833-472-3278 or write to us at:
Dart Container Corporation
500 Hogsback Road
Mason, Michigan 48854
We May Update This Policy.
From time to time we may change our privacy policy.  When we do, we will notify you of any material changes as required by law. We will also post an updated copy here. Please check periodically for updates.
Follow Us on Facebook
Follow Us on Twitter
Connect with Us on LinkedIn
Watch our Videos on YouTube
Region Select
United States
Canada (English)
Canada (français)
Canada (English)
Canada (français)
Canada (English)
Canada (français)
Canada (English)
Canada (français)
